Guide to the The Exit Art Archive 1982 - 2011 MSS 343
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II: Jeanette Ingberman Files
  - Subseries A: Jeanette Ingberman Exhibition Files
    - Monumental Drawings [1999.04]: Press Release, Press Clippings (Box 141, Folder 7)
    - Choice 99 [1999.05]: Promotional Materials (Box 141, Folder 8)
    - What is going on in Sarajevo? [1999.06]: Event Programs, December 5, 1999 (Box 141, Folder 9)
    - The End [2000.01]: Promotional Materials [Photographs] (Box 141, Folder 10)
    - Neo [2000.02]: Promotional Materials [Photographs] (Box 141, Folder 11)
    - Paradise Now [2000.03]: Promotional Materials, Exhibition Catalogue (Box 141, Folder 12)
    - Listening for the Dropa: Event Postcards, June 10, 2000 (Box 142, Folder 1)
    - Coded Bodies [2000.04]: Promotional Materials (Box 142, Folder 2)
    - Collector's Choice [2000.05]: Promotional Materials (Box 142, Folder 3)
    - Body and The East [2001.01]: Promotional Materials, Moderna galerija Ljubljana / Museum of Modern Art Exhibition Book (Box 142, Folder 4)
    - Danger [2001.02]: Promotional Materials (Box 142, Folder 5)
    - Festival of Solitude [2001.03]: Promotional Materials (Box 142, Folder 6)
    - The LP Show [2001.04]: Research Books, 1999, 2000 (Box 142, Folder 7)
      Kohler, Eric. In the Groove: Vintage Record Graphics, 1940-1960. Chronicle Books: San Francisco, CA. 1999.
      McKnight-Trontz, Jennifer and Alex Steinweiss. For the Record: The Life and Work of Alex Steinweiss, Inventor of the Album Cover. Princeton Architectural Press: New York, NY. 2000.
    - The LP Show [2001.04]: Promotional Materials (Box 142, Folder 8)
    - JVC Jazz Festival [2001.05]: Promotional Materials (Box 142, Folder 9)
    - Spunky [2001.06]: Promotional Materials (Box 142, Folder 10)
    - Boomerang [2001.07]: Invitations, Press Release (Box 142, Folder 11)
    - Reactions [2002.01]: Research Books (Box 142, Folder 12)
      9-11: Artists Respond, Volume One. Dark Horse Comics, Inc.: Milwaukie, OR. January 2002.
      9-11, September 11th 2001: The World's Finest Comic Book Writers & Artists Tell Stories to Remember. DC Comics: New York, NY. 2002.
    - Reactions [2002.01]: Promotional Materials (Box 142, Folder 13)
    - Show People [2002.02]: Promotional Materials (Box 142, Folder 14)
    - The Reconstruction [2003.01]: Promotional Materials (Box 143, Folder 1)
    - The L Factor [2003.02]: Promotional Materials (Box 143, Folder 2)
    - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Promotional Materials (Box 143, Folder 3)
    - Public Execution [2004.02]: Promotional Materials (Box 143, Folder 4)
    - The Presidency [2004.03]: Promotional Materials (Box 143, Folder 5)
    - The Print Show [2004.04]: Invitations, Press Release (Box 143, Folder 6)
    - Other America [2005.01]: Invitations, Call For Proposals, 2004, 2005 (Box 143, Folder 7)
    - prayingproject [2005.02]: Promotional Materials (Box 143, Folder 8)
    - Homomuseum [2005.03]: Promotional Materials, 2004, 2005 (Box 143, Folder 9)
    - Traffic [2005.04]: Call For Proposals, Press Release (Box 143, Folder 10)
    - The Studio Visit [2006.01]: Invitations, January 2006 (Box 143, Folder 11)
    - The Drop [2006.02]: Invitations, April 2006 (Box 143, Folder 12)
    - Wild Girls [2006.03]: Invitations, Program, June - July 2006 (Box 143, Folder 13)
    - Interplay [2006.06]: Invitations, Flyers, Program (Box 143, Folder 14)
    - Renegades [2006.07]: Invitations, Exhibition Map, Serious Games Program, December 2006 (Box 143, Folder 15)
    - The Building Show [2007.01]: Invitations, Time Out NY Advertisement, Construct Program (Box 143, Folder 16)
    - Object of Desire: Postcard, Program, April 20, 2007 (Box 143, Folder 17)
    - Killing Time [2007.02]: Promotional Materials, Tropical Area Programs, El Nombre de la Rosa Notebook (Box 143, Folder 18)
    - 25th Anniversary Benefit Auction: Invitations, Auction Lists, April - May 2007 (Box 144, Folder 1)
    - Sultana's Dream [2007.03]: Promotional Materials, Exhibition Catalogue (Box 144, Folder 2)
    - Electric Lab [2007.04]: Promotional Materials (Box 144, Folder 3)
    - Love/War/Sex [2007.05]: Promotional Materials (Box 144, Folder 4)
    - Trickster Theater, Cannon Dialogues: Programs, January 26, 2008 (Box 144, Folder 5)
    - Trickster Theater, Confessions of the Face: Programs, July 29, 2008 (Box 144, Folder 6)
    - Brainwave: Common Senses [2008.01]: Call For Proposals, Promotional Materials, 2007, 2008 (Box 144, Folder 7)
    - Environmental Performance Actions [2008.02]: Invitation, March 2008 (Box 144, Folder 8)
    - Expose Benefit Auction: Invitations, Event Programs, May 1, 2008 (Box 144, Folder 9)
    - Trickster Theater, Somehow: Programs, April 16-17, 2008 (Box 144, Folder 10)
    - Charles Juhasz-Alvarado: Complicated Stories [2008.03]: Promotional Materials (Box 144, Folder 11)
    - Trickster Theater, Still Life: Programs, July 11-12, 2008 (Box 144, Folder 12)
    - Summer Mixtape Volume 1 [2008.05]: Promotional Materials (Box 144, Folder 13)
    - the house is small but THE WELCOME IS BIG [2008.06]: Postcards, September 2008 (Box 144, Folder 14)
    - Signs of Change [2008.07]: Promotional Materials (Box 144, Folder 15)
    - Signs of Change [2008.07]: Exhibition Book by Dara Greenwald and Josh MacPhee, 2010 (Box 145, Folder 1)
    - The Labyrinth Wall [2008.08]: Press Clippings (Box 145, Folder 2)
    - Corpus Extremus (LIFE+) [2009.01]: Promotional Materials (Box 145, Folder 3)
    - Vertical Gardens [2009.02]: Promotional Materials (Box 145, Folder 4)
    - Galeria de la Raza, Renegades: Postcard Flyers, April 18, 2009 (Box 145, Folder 5)
    - Speakeasy Benefit Auction: Invitations, Auction List, Programs, April 28, 2009 (Box 145, Folder 6)
    - Negritude [2009.03]: Promotional Materials (Box 145, Folder 7)
    - The End of Oil [2009.04]: Press Clippings (Box 145, Folder 8)
    - Regina Jose Galindo [2009.05]: Promotional Materials (Box 145, Folder 9)
    - Performance In Crisis [2009.06]: Programs, Flyer (Box 145, Folder 10)
    - America For Sale [2009.07]: Press Release, August 29, 2009 (Box 145, Folder 11)
    - Trickster Theater, I Want to Be a Painting: Invitation, Confessions of the Face Flyers, 2009 (Box 145, Folder 12)
    - Exit Art Benefit - Print Portfolios Retrospective: Invitations, January 6, 2010 (Box 145, Folder 13)
    - Waterpod [2010.01]: Time Out New York Ad Spot, January 14-20, 2010 (Box 145, Folder 14)
    - New Mirrors [2010.02]: Exhibition Newspapers, Brooklyn Rail Article (Box 145, Folder 15)
    - Global/National [2010.03]: Promotional Materials (Box 145, Folder 16)
    - ecoartspace - What Matters Most? NYC Benefit: Postcards, Pamphlets, Purchase Form, April 2010 (Box 145, Folder 17)
    - Exit Art Ecstasy Benefit Auction: Invitations, June 7, 2010 (Box 145, Folder 18)
    - Ecoaesthetic [2010.04]: Promotional Materials (Box 145, Folder 19)
    - Rafael Sanchez: Postcards, Programs, June 2010 (Box 145, Folder 20)
    - Consume [2010.05]: Flyers, 10th Annual Media That Matters Invitations (Box 145, Folder 21)
    - Alternative Histories [2010.06]: Invitations, Public Programs (Box 145, Folder 22)
    - Rockefeller Foundation NYC Cultural Innovation Fund Grantees - NY Times Advertisement, October 6, 2010 (Box 145, Folder 23)
  - Subseries B: Jeanette Ingberman Personal Files
    - Correpondence and Ephemera I, 1983 - 1986 (Box 146, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence and Ephemera II, 1987 - 1989 (Box 146, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence and Ephemera III, 1990 - 1991 (Box 146, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence and Ephemera IV, 1992 (Box 146, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence and Ephemera V, 1992 - 1993 (Box 146, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence and Ephemera VI, 1994 (Box 146, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence and Ephemera VII, 1995 (Box 147, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence and Ephemera VIII, 1996 - 1997 (Box 147, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence and Ephemera IX, 1998 (Box 147, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence and Ephemera X, 1999 - 2000 (Box 147, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence and Ephemera XI, 2001 - 2003 (Box 147, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence and Ephemera XII, 2004 (Box 148, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence and Ephemera XIII, 2005 (Box 148, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence and Ephemera XIV, 2006 - 2008 (Box 148, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence and Ephemera XV, 2009 - 2010 (Box 148, Folder 4)
  - Subseries C: Jeanette Ingberman Administrative Files
    - Business Cards, undated (Box 148, Folder 5)
    - Compositions Notebook, undated (Box 148, Folder 6)
    - Exit Art Timesheets, 2001 - 2002 (Box 148, Folder 7)
    - Exit Art Press Clippings [1 of 2], 2000 - 2006 (Box 148, Folder 8)
    - Exit Art Press Clippings [2 of 2], 2000 - 2006 (Box 149, Folder 1)
- Series III: Potential Exhibitions
  Series III: Potential Exhibitions consists of unrealized exhibitions. Record type includes research and artist profiles, and the series is arranged alphabetically by project title.
  - Alison Saar, 1992 (Box 149, Folder 2)
  - Algerian Theater, 1993, 1994 (Box 149, Folder 3)
  - Ana Mendieta, 1984 - 1985 (Box 149, Folder 4)
  - Animals in the Arsenal: "Art for Animals' Sake" by Bob Woods, 1981 (Box 149, Folder 5)
  - Animals in the Arsenal: Censorship Panel, The New York Public Library, 1984 (Box 149, Folder 6)
  - Animals in the Arsenal: Correspondence, 1981 (Box 149, Folder 7)
  - Animals in the Arsenal: "Crucified Coyote - He Died Because of Our Sins" by Paulette Nenner, February 28, 1981 (Box 149, Folder 8)
  - Animals in the Arsenal: Heresies 3rd Annual Art Benefit, 1982 (Box 149, Folder 9)
  - Animals in the Arsenal: Invitations, Press Release, January 28, 1981; March 4, 1981 (Box 149, Folder 10)
  - Animals in the Arsenal: Legal, 1981 (Box 149, Folder 11)
  - Animals in the Arsenal: Press Clippings, 1981 (Box 149, Folder 12)
  - Animals in the Arsenal: Reproduced Images, 1981 (Box 149, Folder 13)
  - Averty-Kovacs: Correspondence - Anne Marie Duguet, 2000 (Box 149, Folder 14)
  - Averty-Kovacs: Funding, 2000 (Box 149, Folder 15)
  - Averty-Kovacs: Research, 2000 (Box 149, Folder 16)
  - Jean-Christophe Averty by Anne-Marie Duguet, 1991 (Box 149, Folder 17)
  - The Collective Collection, 1988 - 1989 (Box 149, Folder 18)
  - Cult Films: Occult Film Forum by Papo Colo, undated (Box 150, Folder 1)
  - Daryl Chin, 1993, 1994 (Box 150, Folder 2)
  - Edwin Torres: "Gecko Suite", 1998 (Box 150, Folder 3)
  - "Futurama: An Annual International, Collaboratively Curated Event" [Proposal Drafts], 1998 - 1999 (Box 150, Folder 4)
  - "Futurama: An Annual International, Collaboratively Curated Event" [Proposal Finals Drafts], 1999 (Box 150, Folder 5)
  - Futurama: Budget, undated (Box 150, Folder 6)
  - Futurama: Correspondence, 1997 - 2000 (Box 150, Folder 7)
  - Futurama: International Visitors, 1997 (Box 150, Folder 8)
  - Futurama: "Jeanette International - Hans Ulrich Obrist", 1995 - 1997 (Box 150, Folder 9)
  - Helio Oiticica: Budget, 1993 - 1994 (Box 150, Folder 10)
  - Helio Oiticica: Contract, 1994 (Box 150, Folder 11)
  - Helio Oiticica: Correspondence, 1994 (Box 150, Folder 12)
  - Helio Oiticica: Research, 1993 - 1994 (Box 150, Folder 13)
  - History of Hip Hop: Administrative File, 1999 (Box 150, Folder 14)
  - History of Hip Hop: Artist File, 1999 (Box 151, Folder 1)
  - History of Hip Hop: Graffiti Art Catalogues, 1983, 1999 (Box 151, Folder 2)
  - History of Hip Hop: "Hip-Hop Exhibit Strategic Marketing Overview" by Visual Arts Marketing Consultant, September 21, 1999 (Box 151, Folder 3)
  - History of Hip Hop: "Keepin' It Real - Resistance and Reputation in Hip Hop Graffiti Social Networks" by Amy Zimmer [Senior Essay - Department of Anthropology, Yale University], April 23, 1998 (Box 151, Folder 4)
  - History of Hip Hop: Made Men Entertainment, Inc. Proposal, undated (Box 151, Folder 5)
  - History of Hip Hop: "Mapping the Commodification of Hip Hop Culture and The Commercial Power of Hip Hop" by Howie H. Chen [Seminar Thesis], 1998 (Box 151, Folder 6)
  - History of Hip Hop: Research [1 of 3], 1998 - 1999 (Box 151, Folder 7)
  - History of Hip Hop: Research [2 of 3], 1998 - 1999 (Box 151, Folder 8)
  - History of Hip Hop: Research [3 of 3], 1998 - 1999 (Box 151, Folder 9)
  - Hollywood Props: Research, 2003, 2004 (Box 151, Folder 10)
  - The Kremlin Show: Artists List & Proposal, 1989 (Box 151, Folder 11)
  - The Kremlin Show: Funding, 1989 (Box 152, Folder 1)
  - The Kremlin Show: Research, 1989 (Box 152, Folder 2)
  - Man Ray: His Influence on French and American Artists, 1994 (Box 152, Folder 3)
  - Marcel Duchamp: Walker Art Center, 1994 (Box 152, Folder 4)
  - Marginal Artists: Artist Resumes, [1985] (Box 152, Folder 5)
  - Marginal Artists: Publication Funding, 1985 (Box 152, Folder 6)
  - Mechanical Sculpture / Electrifying: Amorphic Robot Works by Chico MacMurtrie, 1997 (Box 152, Folder 7)
  - Mechanical Sculpture / Electrifying: Artists Considered Lists, 1994 (Box 152, Folder 8)
  - Mechanical Sculpture / Electrifying: Artists Files A - J, 1996 - 1997 (Box 152, Folder 9)
  - Mechanical Sculpture / Electrifying: Artists Files K - Z, 1996 - 1997 (Box 153, Folder 1)
  - Mechanical Sculpture / Electrifying: Correspondence, 1994 - 1996 (Box 153, Folder 2)
  - Mechanical Sculpture / Electrifying: Research, 1983, 1992 - 1994 (Box 153, Folder 3)
  - Mechanical Sculpture / Electrifying: Robert Chambers, [1996 - 1997] (Box 153, Folder 4)
  - Mechanical Sculpture / Electrifying: Timothy Brower's "Push Me Pull You" (Box 153, Folder 5)
  - Nick Zedd: Filmography & Promotional Materials, [1986] (Box 153, Folder 6)
  - PERFORMANCES NOT TO BE SEEN: Administrative File, 1983 (Box 153, Folder 7)
  - PERFORMANCES NOT TO BE SEEN: Artist Files [Labeled Empty Folders], undated (Box 153, Folder 8)
  - PERFORMANCES NOT TO BE SEEN: Composition Notebook, undated (Box 153, Folder 9)
  - PERFORMANCES NOT TO BE SEEN: Adrian Piper [Photographs], February 27, 1986 (Box 153, Folder 10)
  - PERFORMANCES NOT TO BE SEEN: Autobiography of Alan Sonfist, 1975 (Box 153, Folder 11)
  - PERFORMANCES NOT TO BE SEEN: Ben Vautier, 1983 (Box 153, Folder 12)
  - PERFORMANCES NOT TO BE SEEN: Bonnie Sherk, 1981, 1985 (Box 153, Folder 13)
  - PERFORMANCES NOT TO BE SEEN: Charlotte Moorman Proclamation, January 5, 1989 (Box 153, Folder 14)
  - PERFORMANCES NOT TO BE SEEN: Dennis Oppenheim [Photographs], August 1983 (Box 153, Folder 15)
  - PERFORMANCES NOT TO BE SEEN: Donna Henes [Photographs], 1983 (Box 153, Folder 16)
  - PERFORMANCES NOT TO BE SEEN: Eleanor Antin, 1985 (Box 153, Folder 17)
  - PERFORMANCES NOT TO BE SEEN: Geoffrey Hendricks [Photographs], 1974, 1978 (Box 153, Folder 18)
  - PERFORMANCES NOT TO BE SEEN: Hsieh Tehching, April 17, 1985 (Box 154, Folder 1)
  - PERFORMANCES NOT TO BE SEEN: Linda Montano, 1975, 1990 (Box 154, Folder 2)
  - PERFORMANCES NOT TO BE SEEN: Lucas Samaras for ARTnews, April 1976 (Box 154, Folder 3)
  - PERFORMANCES NOT TO BE SEEN: Lynn Hershman [Photographs], January 9, 1988 (Box 154, Folder 4)
  - PERFORMANCES NOT TO BE SEEN: Martha Wilson Statement, undated (Box 154, Folder 5)
  - PERFORMANCES NOT TO BE SEEN: Robert Filliou, 1983, 1985 (Box 154, Folder 6)
  - PERFORMANCES NOT TO BE SEEN: Tom Marioni, 1983 (Box 154, Folder 7)
  - PERFORMANCES NOT TO BE SEEN: Vito Acconci, 1983, 1985 (Box 154, Folder 8)
  - PERFORMANCES NOT TO BE SEEN: Yoko Ono, June 9, 1983 (Box 154, Folder 9)
  - Persuasion: Clio Award Winners, 1995, 1999 (Box 154, Folder 10)
  - Persuasion: Clio Short List - The 40th Annual Clio Awards Advertising Festival, 1999 (Box 154, Folder 11)
  - Persuasion: Correspondence, 1996 - 1999 (Box 154, Folder 12)
  - Persuasion: Project Description & Expenses, October 1999; Spring 2000 (Box 154, Folder 13)
  - Persuasion: Research - Art Meets Ads by Jürgen Harten and Michael Schirner, 1993 (Box 154, Folder 14)
  - Persuasion: Research - Clippings, 1999 (Box 154, Folder 15)
  - Persuasion: Research - Magazines, 1997, 1999 (Box 154, Folder 16)
  - S/M: Artist & Research File, 1995 (Box 155, Folder 1)
  - S/M: Artist & Research File - Comics & Zines [1 of 2], 1993, 1995 (Box 155, Folder 2)
    File Contents
    F. Saudelli, The Blonde. Volume Two: "Bondage Palace." Eros Comix: Seattle, WA. 1993.
    Rodriguez, Spain. SHE Comics: An Anthology of Big Bitch. Last Gasp of San Francisco: San Francisco, CA. 1993.
    Sandbox: Creative + Subversive Play. #3: Fear + Transformation Issue. Sandbox: Brooklyn, NY. 1995.
  - S/M: Artist & Research File - Comics & Zines [2 of 2], 1993 - 1995 (Box 155, Folder 3)
    Diana, Mike C. Superfly #1. Michael Hunt Publications: Bensenville, IL. 1993.
    French, Renée. Grit Bath #2. Fantagraphics Books, Inc.: Seattle, WA. January 1994.
    Kiely, Molly. Diary of a Dominatrix #1. Eros Comix: Seattle, WA. March 1993.
    Kiely, Molly. Diary of a Dominatrix #2. Eros Comix: Seattle, WA. January 1994.
    Mead, Stu and Frank Gaard. Man Bag No. 2. Stuart Robinson Mead, Inc.: Minneapolis, MN. [undated].
    Mead, Stu and Frank Gaard. Man Bag No. 3. Stuart Robinson Mead, Inc.: Minneapolis, MN. 1994. [2 copies]
    Mead, Stu and Frank Gaard. Man Bag No. 4. Stuart Robinson Mead, Inc.: Minneapolis, MN. 1995.
    Mead, Stu and Frank Gaard. Man Bag No. 5. Stuart Robinson Mead, Inc.: Minneapolis, MN. [undated].
  - Spoken Word / Music: Curators David Byrne & Robert Coe, undated, 1994 (Box 155, Folder 4)
  - Surrealists: Program Proposals, 1997 (Box 155, Folder 5)
  - Surrealists: Research [1 of 2], [1997] (Box 155, Folder 6)
  - Surrealists: Research [2 of 2], [1997] (Box 155, Folder 7)
  - Techno Show: Kathy Brew, Director of Thundergulch - New Media Arts Initiative, 1999 (Box 155, Folder 8)
  - Techno Show: Research (Box 155, Folder 9)
  - Techno Show: Research - No1se: Universal Language, Pattern Recognition, Data Synaesthetics - A Series of Exhibitions about Information and Transformation curated by Adam Lowe and Simon Schaffer, January 28, 2000 (Box 156, Folder 1)
  - Toys 'n Noise / Games Exhibition: Research, 1999 - 2000 (Box 156, Folder 2)
  - Toys 'n Noise / Games Exhibition: Research - Bringing Down the House by Daniel Canogar, 1995 (Box 156, Folder 3)
  - Under the Influence: Artist List, undated (Box 156, Folder 4)
  - "Video Research at Other Spaces" [1 of 2], 1998 - 2000 (Box 156, Folder 5)
  - "Video Research at Other Spaces" [2 of 2], 1998 - 2000 (Box 156, Folder 6)
  - Young Curators, 1998 - 2000 (Box 156, Folder 7)
- OVERSIZE Series V: Photographic Materials
  - Subseries A: Exhibition Photographs
    - Immigrants and Refugees / Heroes or Villains [1987.01] [2 of 2], undated